{
    "subject": "resource/Netviewer",
    "predicate": "property/homepage",
    "object": "http://netviewer.com",
    "human_readable": "The homepage of Netviewer is http://netviewer.com.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9150884747505188,
            "question": "What is the URL of Netviewer's homepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8556193709373474,
            "question": "Where can you find the Netviewer homepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8332513570785522,
            "question": "How do you access Netviewer's homepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7518961429595947,
            "question": "What URL leads to Netviewer's primary page?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7179949879646301,
            "question": "What is the web address for accessing Netviewer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6975829601287842,
            "question": "What is the web location for Netviewer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6823602318763733,
            "question": "Where online can you visit Netviewer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6599164009094238,
            "question": "Give the internet address for visiting Netviewer."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6169254779815674,
            "question": "Provide the internet address of Netviewer's main page."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5867998003959656,
            "question": "If you want to visit Netviewer, what website should you go to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The homepage of Netviewer is http://netviewer.com.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6515_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Provide the internet address of Netviewer's main page.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6515_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give the internet address for visiting Netviewer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6515_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where online can you visit Netviewer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6515_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6515_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6515_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6515_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6515_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6515_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6515_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6515_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6515_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6515_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6515_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text does not mention the homepage URL for Netviewer. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: None of the provided documents contain information about Netviewer's homepage URL. Therefore, the statement \"The homepage of Netviewer is http://netviewer.com\" cannot be confirmed as correct based on the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}